KAREL VERSCHRAEGEN

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



karelverschraegen.com



github.com/KarelVerschraegen/



karelverschraegenbiz@gmail.com



Ghent, Belgium

PROFILE

I have spent the last 3.5+ years focused on all aspects of software development, ranging from building applications in React to setting up GraphQL resolvers and MongoDB databases.

These days, I help solve equipment management problems in the audiovisual industry with a focus on React and NestJS with GraphQL.

Besides work, you'll find me in a swimming pool, skiing on the slopes, or quoting "The Office! I love traveling and exploring the hidden gems each city has to offer.

SKILLS

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication and coordination
- Problem solver
- Team player
- Leadership
- Curiosity

HARD SKILLS

- TypeScript
- React
- GraphQL
- NestJS / NodeJS
- MongoDB / PostgreSQL

EDUCATION

APPLIED COMPUTER SCIENCE

Hogeschool Gent (2016 - 2019)

EXPERIENCE

TECH LEAD - CHEQROOM

July 2022 - Present

- Manage and host scrum ceremonies (stand-ups, sprint reviews, ...)
- Communicate and coordinate feature releases and bug fixes
- Unblock team members, provide feedback and technical insights
- Tackle technical debt, large refactors and cleaning up legacy code

FULL STACK DEVELOPER - CHEQROOM

July 2019 - July 2022

- Set up communication layer between our legacy Knockout and new React codebase
- Build out design system and accompanying component library
- Set up and deploy GraphQL microservices on AWS
- Automate the deployment process via GitHub Actions

INTERN - RIALTO

February 2019 - May 2019

- Learn React, Redux and TypeScript
- Build a floorplan drawing tool based on SVG's